Hello Sir tell me about Duba Duba, first I have
updated Outlook,
so Rahul, that is that the market is
not ready to stop, but it is very very,
pick up the call and you are seeing the online form for
trying to generate, hi son, this to me, what should I say,
and to wrong, but bank, sir, very
weak and gaunt metal, let me tell you this,
when dollar showing research and friends and
powerful territory, whatever reminder comes in dollar, then there is
emerging markets end also, even then the
trading profit and loss of the conference is,
yes here also I want to say that
Anil Singh's calls, if we give them after hedging, then it is
for trading,
you are on both sides, keep a margin of two days in it,
which will be stop loss or Twitter, then this is
for you, this has to be done between us and you,
and that is why it is said that if you do
not do search operations here, then there is a stop loss in one hand, then
you will have to bear,
sir, what I am saying is absolutely important,
he left from here with three friends taking
₹500, then you people will keep saying
that administration did not call
If calling is fair to me, then I am
telling you that
my WhatsApp does not mean that
I am in the temple, I am bullish, I am
with you. I am telling you this because here
I am wearing a tractor cap or an
inverter or not because the
rewards from here are not favorable for investors. You are right,
which is absolutely perfect and absolutely
correct that looking at the depression,
for different investments from trading point of view also, you just need to continuously
subscribe to Godrej Consumer. Good staff was appointed at 266 67294. I
kept my stoploss of 1575 and the one I gave you
and I went to 1617 four to five times, you
can make profit there. In front of that, Reliance
Buy was given at 1888. Shop Love from you. I still
think that this is a little
overtraining in this. Reliance Candy Crush Smart
Back to Market Global Reliance and
Strong and along with it, brother, what deal
Khedira has done 497 brother, the target is 11010,
now one day you can book profit.  UPA
coalition bank you two my brother friend please
start in a week so please tell me so the first solution will be
sir for you ICICI Lombard
buy at 1595 to 1662 there is surplus of
1575 target of 1655 second biodata chemical buy at 498
second take at 490 dream defect target of 515
in sale effect is parasale
send in dowry for 102 stoploss target of 92
and second Bank of Baroda send at 64064
hobby of 25 paise in 66 561 lean forward
from school where to buy in two and
click on it Islam butt this is
for you to buy from 1595 to
1622 you have to buy 15 subscribe
around ₹100 10 aa padhara
is appropriate for
subscription and subscribe here
Shreya Ghoshal with balance machine saaf
detiye karte hain are held in stadium
[music]
Ajay